Here are 16 of my favorite closes.
So this is the what's your main concern close.
This is the reason close.
This is the hypothetical close.
This is the zoom out close.
This is the one to 10 close.
This is the best case worst case close.
This is the some now more later close.
This is the future favorite close.
This is the cheap comparison close.
This is the good fast cheap close.
This is the mechanic close.
This is the surgeon secretary close.
This is the game plan close.
And this is the both options are risk-free close.
This is the you're not gonna struggle forever, right?
Close.
This is the closer or further close.
And this is the follow if you like selling close.